buybuybaby.com 2016-04-30

# Privacy Policy

At buybuy BABY we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, and therefore we do not sell or rent the information our customers provide to any third party. Further, we do not share the information that you provide to us with any third parties for their direct marketing purposes without first providing you the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of such sharing. You may request information about how we share information consistent with this Privacy Policy by contacting us at: [privacy.information@buybuybaby.com](mailto:privacy.information@buybuybaby.com).

The www.buybuybaby.com web site (the **"Site"** ) is owned by Buy Buy Baby, Inc. We refer to Buy Buy Baby, Inc. as the "Company," " **we** ," " **us** " or " **our**." The Company’s parent, Bed Bath & Beyond Inc. ("Bed Bath & Beyond"), assists with the operation and maintenance of the Site.

This page sets forth our policies regarding the use and disclosure of information we collect from or are able to obtain about the Site’s users. We refer to these policies as our " **Privacy Policy**." In addition to the lower case words "we", "us" and "our" defined above, you will notice that we capitalize certain words in this Privacy Policy even though the rules of grammar do not require that they be capitalized. We do this because these words have specific meanings in this Privacy Policy. These specific meanings are found where the capitalized words are placed in bold text and inside quotation marks.

We hope this Privacy Policy will answer your questions regarding how we treat information gathered from our Site. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, other than requests for our information sharing practices as described in the first paragraph above, please feel free to contact us at [customer.service@buybuybaby.com](mailto:customer.service@buybuybaby.com); or, if you wish to exclude the information that you provide to us from our direct marketing programs including e-mail, please refer to the section titled "How to Opt-Out," below.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain through means other than the Site, such as by phone or postal mail. But please note that information including your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card number that you provide to us through such means will be treated in accordance with the first paragraph above and our use of such information will be consistent with this Privacy Policy. By accessing and using the Site you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use the Site. Furthermore, by providing us with information on this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

As we update and diversify our products and services, this Privacy Policy may change. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page for updates periodically. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here. Unless the law otherwise requires, we do not provide notice of changes to this Privacy Policy and your use of the Site following any posted changes will indicate your acceptance of such changes. **This Privacy Policy became effective in 1999, and was most recently changed on March 25, 2016.** The last change to this policy was:

  * Clarification regarding the types of information collected on the Site. 
  * To enhance details regarding how the Site responds to Do Not Track Signals. 
  * Other minor language changes.

### What Information We Actively Collect and Inactively Gather

###  Information You Provide 

In order to process orders efficiently, when you place an order with us or register an account on the Site we actively collect the following information: name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card number. If you prefer not to disclose such information online, you can always place your order by calling 1-877-3-BUY-BABY (1-877-328-9222) or visiting one of our many stores.

We may periodically conduct surveys of visitors to our Site for internal research purposes that may include marketing. This helps us better understand what our customers would like to see from us. If you respond to such surveys, we may ask you for some information and/or may contact you for more information, but only if you have given us permission to do so.

We may also receive information about you from other sources.

### Site Usage Information

We (including through our third party service providers) may inactively collect from you information that is not in the same category as your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, or credit card number. For example, we might track information about the date and time you access the Site, the type of web browser you use, and the web site from which you connect to our Site. We collect and use this and other information (such as demographic data) to analyze and develop our business strategy and to determine how you found out about us, your interests regarding our products and services and how to further improve our Site. We, or a third party, may also collect information from your activities on the Site as well as other sites for the purpose of providing advertisements and other content that is customized to your interests and preferences. This means that our ads may appear on participating web sites based upon your browsing activity. To accomplish all this, and also to allow us to offer our customers streamlined ordering and other useful features, we, as do many web sites, use and allow our third party advertising companies to use the technologies listed below and other similar technologies (the " **Tracking Technologies** "): 

  * **Cookies and Clear GIFs** \- Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies make web surfing easier for you by saving your customer identification information (i.e., username, password, shopping cart information, etc.) while you’re at a site. Cookies also track where you travel on a site and what you look at and purchase. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message. You can learn more about how third party advertising companies use cookies and clear GIFs, including how to opt-out, by clicking [**HERE**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). Please read the explanation carefully should you choose to opt-out using this method.
  * **IP Address Tracking and Clickstream Data** \- In addition to cookies and clear GIFs, our servers automatically collect data about your server’s Internet address when you visit our Site. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or " **IP Address** ", is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you view pages from our Site, our servers may record or "log" your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server also may record the page that linked you to us and related information including any ads you may have clicked on. Such information is known as " **Clickstream Data** ". 
  * **Email Interconnectivity** \- If you receive email from us, we may use certain tools to capture data related to when you open our message, click on any links or banners it contains and make purchases. 

In some cases, we may link the information collected through the Tracking Technologies with certain information that you provide to us. WE WANT TO BE SURE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THAT ACCEPTING TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES ONTO YOUR COMPUTER IN NO WAY GIVES US ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER OR ANY ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU. YOU MAY SET YOUR WEB BROWSER SOFTWARE TO REJECT TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES, BUT, IF YOU DO SO, CERTAIN FUNCTIONALITY OF THE SITE MAY BE AFFECTED. Third parties (including, but not limited to, software vendors, advertisers and fulfillment companies) may also use Tracking Technologies by or through the Site. WE HAVE NO CONTROL OVER WHAT INFORMATION SUCH THIRD PARTIES TRACK OR COLLECT, AND HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY TRACKING, DATA COLLECTION OR OTHER ACTIVITIES OF SUCH THIRD PARTIES. 

### Mobile Device Identifiers

You may be visiting the Site from your mobile device. Certain mobile service providers uniquely identify mobile devices and we or our third-party service providers may receive such information if you access the Site through mobile devices. Some features of the Site may allow for the collection of mobile phone numbers and we may associate that phone number to mobile device identification information. Furthermore, some mobile phone service providers operate systems that pinpoint the physical location of devices that use their service. Depending on the provider, we or our third-party service providers may receive this information.

### Wireless Addresses

If an e-mail address you have provided us is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from us (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the "How to Opt-Out" instructions below). You understand that your wireless carrier’s standard rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions below. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

### Security of the Information You Provide

Among our top priorities is keeping the information you provide to us secure. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt all of the information that you provide to us before it is transmitted to us so that it can be safeguarded as much as possible from being read or recorded as it travels over the Internet. You can tell you are sending information securely by the unbroken key icon or closed lock icon that appears at the bottom of your Internet browser's window. These icons will appear when you are placing an order on our Site. In addition, you will see our Site address change slightly, from http: to https: indicating a secure server connection is being used. The computers that store the information you provide to us are located in a separate facility which employs firewall and security technology. We employ these procedures to help protect that information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

You may be able to create an account on our Site with a username and password, including if you set up a customer account or a registry. We recommend you exercise extreme care in protecting your password information and do not publicly share any of your passwords. You are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of the Site by you or another person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you.

Information that you provide to us will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding such information in the United States may vary and be less stringent than laws of your state or country. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to hold and transmit the information that you provide to us in a safe, confidential and secure environment. If you object to the information that you provide to us being transferred or used in this manner please do not register with or use the Site.

ALTHOUGH WE WILL TAKE (AND REQUIRE OUR THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS TO TAKE) REASONABLE SECURITY PRECAUTIONS TO PROTECT THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US, BECAUSE OF THE OPEN NATURE OF THE INTERNET, WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT SUCH INFORMATION STORED ON SERVERS SUPPORTING THIS SITE, TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM A USER, OR OTHERWISE IN OUR CARE (OR OUR THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS' CARE) WILL BE ABSOLUTELY SAFE FROM INTRUSION BY OTHERS, SUCH AS HACKERS. ACCORDINGLY, WE DISCLAIM ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY THEFT OR LOSS OF, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR DAMAGE TO, OR INTERCEPTION OF ANY DATA OR COMMUNICATIONS. BY USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO ASSUME THESE RISKS.

### How Do We Use the Information that You Provide and We Collect?

We collect information from you for the purposes of fulfilling orders, processing returns and exchanges and providing you with the services you have chosen, providing a high level of customer service, providing you with information we believe may be of interest including mailing our circulars and special offers, for editorial and feedback purposes, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of your behavior, for product development, for content improvement, for protection against fraud and error and to customize the content and layout of the Site (collectively, " **Information Usage Purposes** "). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not knowingly use a mobile phone number for marketing purposes without first obtaining your consent. In performing the Information Usage Purposes, we may combine information we collect on the Site with information we receive from other sources. We do not sell the information that you provide us and we do not disclose such information to any other party, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, information that you transmit to the Site or that we collect from the Site will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and you agree that we may use any such information (together with any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained therein) in any manner, for any purpose, without credit or compensation to you. Without limiting the generality or application of the foregoing, the information that you publish on or through the Baby Registry is governed by specific terms available below under the heading "Baby Registry Information".

### Sharing of Your Information With Our Partners; Transfer of Your Information

We may share the information that you provide to us with our associates and to companies acting as our authorized agents or partners in providing our service or co-branded services to you and in performing Information Usage Purposes. This would include our parent company, Bed Bath & Beyond, but only to the extent it performs or assists in the performance of Information Usage Purposes on our behalf. We screen and reasonably determine to be reputable any third party to whom we disclose such information and we require such third parties to agree to use the information that our customers provide to us only for such specified purposes. Each of our partners must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information that we share with them in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

If we merge, or sell or otherwise transfer our assets, Site or operations, we may disclose or transfer your information in connection with such transaction.

### Baby Registry Information

Baby Registry information is treated differently from information submitted for other purposes on our Site. Registry users may receive additional e-mail communications from us, such as a registry welcome e-mail and follow-up contact after the baby’s expected arrival date. In addition, cookies are used as part of our registry service to save your registry number on your computer. Finally, by registering with us and opting to make your registry available online, your registry information, which includes your name, the state where you live and your baby’s expected arrival date, will be made available to our partners that help provide our services and our co-branded services (including for Information Usage Purposes) as well as search engines and spiders that are not affiliated with us.

Finally, and to illustrate the type of business partner with whom your registry information may be shared, if you have not taken advantage of the applicable opt-out procedure, your registry information (your name, state where you live and baby’s expected arrival date) may be made available to third party gift registry portal sites. We may also share the e-mail address associated with your registry, but solely to enable us and such a third-party registry portal site to link your purchases or other activity with the registry you have established with us. The use of such portal sites is intended to provide your guests with additional means of finding your registry, and to provide you with additional ways to create a registry with us. Any third-party registry portal site with whom an e-mail address is shared as a registry identifier is contractually prohibited from using it for any other purpose not outlined above. In the future, if you wish to opt-out of our sharing your information with such sites, please send an e-mail to [customer.service@buybuybaby.com](mailto:customer.service@buybuybaby.com) clearly indicating such request.

Please review the Site’s Terms and Conditions for more information on the use of the Baby Registry.

### Use of Information in Sweepstakes and Contests

Occasionally, we may run a promotion such as a sweepstakes or a contest (a "Promotion"), and you will be given the opportunity to enter by filling out an entry form, or in some cases, you may be automatically entered by using a designated type of credit card when placing an order in store, online or via phone or, for example, by creating a Baby Registry. Your entry information may be shared with third parties for the limited purposes of administering the sweepstakes and selecting a winner(s) and may be used to notify you in connection with the sweepstakes or contest and to verify your identity. When you enter such a Promotion, you will have the opportunity to consent to receive future communications from us. Since we value your privacy, you will always have the opportunity to stop such communications by opting-out, as detailed above. In addition, some Promotions may have one or more co-sponsors, and you may also be asked upon entry to consent to receive future communications from such co-sponsors. In the event your consent is indicated, the information from your entry will be shared with the co-sponsors. In those situations, the third parties will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies, and we are not responsible for how co-sponsors may use your information. In all events, we will make it clear to you in the entry, order or registration form, before you submit it, whether you are consenting to receive information from any party, and you will be given the opportunity to confirm or withdraw such consent prior to submitting your entry, order or registration.

In any case, where you elect to have us share your information with third parties, such as in the Promotions discussed above, those elections to have your information shared will supersede anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy. 

### How to Opt-out

We will only send e-mail for customer service purposes and to those customers who have indicated that they wish to receive other types of e-mail from us. 

If at any time you wish to stop receiving e-mail from us, you can always remove your name from our mailing list by sending an e-mail to [customer.service@buybuybaby.com](mailto:customer.service@buybuybaby.com) stating that you wish to unsubscribe and indicating in the subject line of the e-mail "NO E-MAIL". Although we will promptly remove your name from our e-mail list upon receiving your request, it is possible that you may still receive e-mails from us that had been initiated prior to your name being removed from our list.

If at any time you do not want to receive offers and/or circulars from us, you can always remove yourself from our mailing list by sending an e-mail to [customer.service@buybuybaby.com](mailto:customer.service@buybuybaby.com), indicating "NO SNAIL MAIL" in the subject line along with your name, address and zip code. Please note that our mailings are prepared in advance of their being sent. Although we will promptly remove your name from our mailing list upon receiving your request, you may still receive mailings from us that had been initiated prior to your name being removed from our list. You can also contact us by mail:

Buy Buy Baby, Inc.  
Attention: Customer Service - Privacy  
Internet Division  
650 Liberty Avenue  
Union, NJ 07083  
customer.service@buybuybaby.com  

THE OPT-OUT RIGHTS AND PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THIS SECTION ARE THE DEFAULT RULES AND PROCEDURES WE USE IN OPERATING THE SITE AND ARE THE STANDARD BY WHICH WE ADHERE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.

### Release of Information to Protect Our Site and Others

We may release the information that you provide to us when we believe, in good faith, that such release is necessary to comply with the law, protect the rights, properties or safety of the Company, our users or others, or enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements.

### Your Account Access Rights

You may review and make changes to the information that you provide to us that is stored in your user account on the Site by visiting the "My Account" area of the Site.

### Intended Users; Use by Children under 13

The Site is not purposefully directed at children under the age of 13 and all products available for sale on the Site are intended to be purchased by adults. We do not collect or maintain information, via the Site or otherwise, from those we actually know are children under 13 years of age. If you notify us that information has been provided by a child under the age of 13, upon verification, we will promptly delete such information.

### Third Party Ad Servers; Links to Other Web Sites

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. The Site also may contain links to other web sites that are not under our control. These links may include the use of so-called "share links." A "share link" is a button and/or text link appearing on our Site that enables the launch of a sharing mechanism whereby you can post links to, and content from, the Site onto social networking web sites such as Facebook. The privacy policies of other web site operators or advertisers may significantly differ from our Privacy Policy. We urge you to read the privacy statements of each and every web site you visit and to contact the third-party web site operators or advertisers directly if you have any questions or concerns about their data collection or privacy policies. WE HAVE NO CONTROL OR INFLUENCE OVER THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF SUCH OTHER WEB SITES AND ADVERTISERS AND WE DO NOT ASSUME ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY THIRD-PARTY WEB SITE OPERATORS’ OR ADVERTISERS’ DATA COLLECTION PRACTICES, THEIR FAILURE TO ABIDE BY THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES OR THE CONTENT OF ANY THIRD PARTY WEB SITES.

### How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals

We do not currently recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include "Do Not Track" instructions. You can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of Tracking Technologies through your browser. However, as noted above in the Site Usage Information section, if you do adjust your privacy preferences, certain functionality of the site may be affected. For more information on Do Not Track please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/)
